Guide to the Association for Union Democracy: Women's Project Records WAG.331
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Subject and Organization Files, 1974-2004, 1947-2004 (Bulk 1980-2002); 14 Linear Feet
  - Women in Union Leadership, c. 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Women of the New York Fire Department: Stories and Struggles, Mar 2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Women Office Workers: Research and Education Project, Inc., 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Women on the Job, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Women on the Job, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Women on the Job, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Women on the Job: Pay Equity, 1987-1990 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Women on the Job Task Force, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Women Union Electricians: A Comparison of Job and Training Experiences of White Women and Women of Color" (A Thesis), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Women, Work and Welfare, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Women's Alliance for Job Equity (WAJE), 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Women's Caucus of the Democratic National Committee: "Gender Gap Issues and What You Need to Know about Them", 1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Women's Enews, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The Women's Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Women's Funds, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Women's History Month, 1990, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Women's Institute for Leadership Development (WILD), 1989-1992 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Women's Legal Defense Fund, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Women's Organizations: Brochures, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Women's Project of Little Rock, AR (Non-Affiliated), undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Words of Wit (Minnesota Women in the Trades), 1993-2000 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Working/Women's Institute, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - World March of Women, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - YWCA of Brooklyn - Planned Parenthood: "Women of Influence", 1993 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - YWCA: Women in Trades Project, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Exhibits and Conferences, 1994, 1998 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 3)